[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who was given a Honorary Academy Award  in 1967?", "correct_answer": "Enos Edward Yakima Canutt", "incorrect_answers": ["Edith Head", "John Gilbert", "Mary Astor"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "One of the two species, comprising the chimpanzee genus, is the Common Chimpanzee. What is the name of the other species?", "correct_answer": "Bonobo chimpanzee", "incorrect_answers": ["Kalapuor chimpanzee", "Lowland chimpanzee", "Highland chimpanzee"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What time of the day do tornadoes most often strike?", "correct_answer": "3 p.m. - 9p.m.", "incorrect_answers": ["12 a.m. - 1 p.m.", "10 p.m. - 3 a.m.", "2 a.m. - 12 p.m"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What was the name of the bartender at Martinis featured in the movie Its a Wonderful Life?", "correct_answer": "Nick", "incorrect_answers": ["Jim", "Joe", "Mac"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Pollution has damaged this great Chinese ancient attraction and it continues to disintegrate.", "correct_answer": "The Terracotta Warriors", "incorrect_answers": ["The Forbidden City", "Tiananmen Square", "The Great Wall"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Saturn is the only ringed planet in the Solar system.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which Peanuts cartoon character said, All I really need is love, but a little chocolate now and then doesnt hurt!?", "correct_answer": "Lucy", "incorrect_answers": ["Charlie Brown", "Linus", "Sally"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Norwegian inventor, Johan Vaaler was granted a patent in Germany, in 1899, for the invention of what?", "correct_answer": "The paperclip", "incorrect_answers": ["The dry cell battery", "The stapler", "Carbon paper"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In what Disney film was the following question asked: What do you want me to do, dress in drag and do the hula?", "correct_answer": "The Lion King", "incorrect_answers": ["Fun and Fancy Free", "Aladdin", "Hercules"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Kelp ash is used in the production of which of the following?", "correct_answer": "Glass", "incorrect_answers": ["Plastic", "Rubber", "Teflon"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This kind of doctor is an expert in such diseases as Lupus, Sjogrens Syndrome, and Dermatomyositis.", "correct_answer": "Rheumatologist", "incorrect_answers": ["Otorrhinolaryngologist", "Internist", "Gastroenterologist"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What year was the movie Miracle released?", "correct_answer": "2004", "incorrect_answers": ["2003", "2002", "2005"]}]